Thank you for watching!
Hello?
Uh, hello?
Uh, this is Huey.
Hello, hold on a second.
Who is this?
Hello?
Can you hear me? Can you hear me?
Yes, I can hear you.
Hello. Hold on a second.
Who is this?
It's been a while.
It's been a while, right?
What?
Wait a minute.
I really don't know.
What?
What? I don't know who that is.
I think my voice might have changed a little.
Oh, really?
Yes, I'm sure.
Let's see...
How long ago?
I'm sorry, how long ago was that?
How long ago did you know him?
Well, I was in charge of it in 2013 or so.
I was in charge?
Oh, okay.
Wait a minute.
By "in charge" do you mean...
My management.
You were in charge?
Yes, I did. Yes, you were.
You must be Mr. Muto.
That theory came true.
So there is a pattern with Mr. Muto.
I was surprised, too.
I haven't heard anything about this, really.
That's right.
It might be the first time since I visited Akasaka Blitz.
Oh, yes, that's right.
Was it last year or something? Was it in 2019?
Yes, it was. Maybe it was.
It's been a while since I saw you live and I was really moved.
Anyway, it's been a while.
It's been a while.
When I saw you at Akasaka Blitz, I thought you were a great singer.
The atmosphere of the live show has changed a lot since I was in charge of it.
But I guess it might have.
At that time, the costumes were ripped to shreds and so on.
Yes, yes. But it has changed. Rather.
So at that time,
I was only thinking about releasing it.
Like, how much I can release.
Anyway.
I was also releasing the drink from my mouth.
Like a pischer.
That's right.
He was discharging all kinds of things, wasn't he?
I don't know...
You know...
There were times when you bought no clothes.
There were times when you didn't have any clothes, right?
That's right.
When I think about it...
You have changed a lot, haven't you?
That's right. You also shot music videos in loincloths, didn't you?
That's right. It was a loincloth.
The whole team ran along the beach in loincloths.
That's right.
Music videos were also shot with ZENRA when Mr. Yanai was shooting, weren't they?
Oh, that's right. That too.
Yes, there was. The pattern that is not in the Third Planet Public Ping Pong.
Zenler TV, which is considered a masterpiece.
Like a French movie, a French movie.
I think it was a music video.
Yes, it was. Something has changed though, a little bit.
I think it's only in the last few years that they finally started to sing properly.
So you don't fly over the speakers to the audience anymore? I don't fly so much now.
I'm trying to make the songs fly into the audience's hearts before they fly out of the speakers.
I don't know, but I'm really getting that way.
I was on stage at that time.
I was doubling for you on stage, wasn't I?
I mean, you were singing backstage, and I was singing in the dark, wearing Hibi's costume, and I was singing face down.
And I was singing with my face down in the dark.
It was a totally unnecessary performance, wasn't it?
It was a totally unnecessary performance.
I felt like I was working really hard on that kind of useless stuff.
We practiced that a lot, didn't we?
Why did you decide to do that?
I don't know.
At the time, the idea of the live performance was that it was something outlandish and interesting.
I wanted to do something bizarre and interesting.I felt like I had to do something bizarre and interesting.
I felt like I had to do something outlandish and interesting.
I thought about what I could do, and that's when I came up with the
I thought about what I could do, and that's when I came up with Operation Doublespeak.
There were a lot of things that happened, you know.
There was the time we were almost late for Samaso.
We had to go somewhere by ourselves.
We didn't know we had to go somewhere, and we were in the dressing room until about how many minutes into the show.
That's right.
We said, "Oh shit, it's time to go on stage," and we all ran and went through the same line with the audience. We went to the stage.
And then we left.
There was a traffic jam before that, I think.
We all had to change trains.
Kumi and Jim got on the same train as the customers.
Kumi and Jim got on the same train as the guests.
There it is.
They came, didn't they?
It's a terrible thing now that I think about it.
How did you do it?
I think I got in a lot of trouble back then.
That's right.
I remember that time when we went out on stage and the microphone was so hot that I thought I didn't have a microphone.
I thought I didn't have a microphone. And the stage was 2 meters or 3 meters high.
And then you dove off the stage, didn't you?
Yeah, I did. We were in a venue where there was a lot of distance between us and the audience.
In the dirt.
Do you remember that?
That's right.
Yeah, it was a big dive.
Was this your first time at Summer Sonny's?
Yes, that's right.
The first time I went to Summer Soni.
You plunged head first into the dirt.
And after that...
I think the microphone wire fell out a little or something.
I got a huge electric shock.
Wait a minute.
Ring-ring-ring-ring, are you okay with this?
Yes, it is.
Yes, indeed.
After the concert, when I was getting really angry, Shui-san came down from the stage after the concert,
He came down to the front and took a dip in the water backstage. It was like a hippopotamus.
There were other performers and stuff. He was getting angry at me for taking a bath in the front row,
I was told, "Don't worry about that, do something about that guy.
I see. He told me to manage him properly.
First of all, he should put on some clothes.
That's interesting.
I've grown up.
That's right.
He used to take me to a pub like Senbero.
We used to go there a lot, that's for sure. We talked a lot there.
Like Odo Yokocho in Shinjuku.
Have you ever been to a Chinese restaurant in Shimokita?
Is it a new garden?
Yes, I did. But I still go there.
Really? So nothing has changed in that area?
Nothing has changed at all.
I just started singing more. You mean you started to focus on singing.
At that time, I felt like I was saying that the more I was pushed into a corner, the better songs I could write.
I was thinking that it's better to be in a bad situation in your private life.
But you're right. That may not change.
It won't change?
But there are a lot of dangerous situations.
But I don't think much has changed.
I see.
I think it's better if something strange happens.
I can write songs.
I think I can write songs more when something bizarre is happening.
You were cooking a lot back then, weren't you?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
And at that time, there were a lot of names of dishes in the lyrics.
but...
Oh, yes, that's right.
There were a lot of songs about food, like "omelette" and "omelette" and so on.
Chicken and cabbage and whatnot...
Yes, that's true.
Yes, I still sing about rice.
That desire for food is probably stronger than other people's.
I think that's good.
I want to eat good food.
I think I work hard and write songs to eat good food.
I had a lot of fun.
I see.
Yes, I did.
It didn't feel like work.
But there were times when it was a bit difficult to maintain hygiene.
But there were things like that.
There were things like that.
Yes, there were things like that.
Oh. So it was more interesting.
No, it was something really interesting.
Just watching Mr. Q was fun.
Ha-ha-ha. Well, I guess you're right.
Even I was moved at every live performance.
Wow.
About 30 minutes.
The last song we sang was the last song of the show, and I was so moved, and Flare, who is in charge of the show now, was crying beside me.
I don't know, Marina was crying.I don't know, Marina was crying.
Is it a love song at the end of the world or something? Ah, yes. Yes, they did. It was recently released about two years ago. Finally.
I've been recruited.
You were doing it, weren't you?
That's right.
Yes, we were.
I kind of remember we didn't have quite a lot of money at the time.
Yes, yes, yes.
I didn't have a lot of money either.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
So it was really fun to have that feeling with you.
Oh, it's true that you had some debts, too.
That's right.
I was in debt, wasn't I?
I wrote a song about being a bad person.
Yes, that's true.
But...
I liked it that way.
I don't know...
It's not good, but I liked it, and I guess it could easily be a song.
I think that kind of depraved, human-like quality of a human being can easily be used in a song,
That kind of thing can easily be used as lyrics.
That's right.
Those were the days.
I miss those days. There were various situations that were really easy to write songs about.
Hey, Mr. Muto, when did you quit your previous company?
Hmmm.
You were there after I left.
You were at the company, weren't you? That's right, I left in 2017.
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
I got married.
I see, I see. Oh, that's right, that's right. That. That's what I want to say. You've been hiding it from me for so long.
I was asking him for advice on love, but he hid it from me. I felt betrayed. No, no, no, no, no, no.
We talked about love all the time. But somehow, yes.
I was thinking about it, yes. Did you notice that? Yes, I did.
There was something strange about it.
But the people in the company didn't notice it at all, I guess.
No one noticed.
That's right.
So I got married and had a baby without telling Shu.
That's right. You got married and had a child without telling me.
That's right.
Yes, yes. That's right.
Yes, that's right. There's something else I haven't told you, but we have another child now.
Thank you very much. Recently?
But he is already 3 years old. He's a tata, isn't he?
Sorry for the ego report, but...
Congratulations. That's amazing. So you are a father of two?
Yes, that's right.
Do you remember me?
I remember you very well.
Really?
But didn't we ever talk? We were in the same office.
No, I have talked to you a few times.
I remember you smiling at me when we were talking at a drinking party or something.
Yes, that's right. He seemed like he was on the up-and-up. I thought I was "cool," but I was cool, wasn't I?
I am ashamed of myself for thinking I was "cool.
But even now, when Mr. Hiiran appears on TV.
I'm sure I'll hear from you soon.
Ah!
Hugh is on TV! Like that.
Oh, I'm glad to hear that.
If you ever have kids...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Would you name it something like Hughie?
No!
Huey... but I don't want to name him Stretcher Stick.
I don't think I'd want to name him Stretcher Stick.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Stretching pole... well, from your point of view...
What do you think of Ishizaki's current outfit?
Well, I feel like... the world has finally met her. Oh, you mean in a good way? In a good way.
Finally...
I don't think the content of the song is that different from back then.
The way he sings is almost the same. I'd like to say that I think people are finally starting to understand the merits of the song.
So it seems to be spreading because it's just a little bit.
It seems to be spreading a lot.
There have been a lot of movies.
I've even been in a few movies.
I don't think it's bad.
I don't think so. I don't think so.
No, I don't think it's bad at all.
I don't feel bad at all.
Have things changed since then?
I don't know.
Well...
So, you know...
Singing.
I've learned to sing better. It's going to be this again.
It's the lyrics, right?
I'm starting to realize that it's all about the lyrics.
I think that's probably the biggest thing.
I'd love to come back for a drink. Let's go.
It's been a while since you've been to this motley crew.
Thank you. Thank you. I'll call you later.
Thank you very much.